

KONTAK

- Kp Pondok Rt 01 Rw 03 Sindang jaya, Pasar Kemis Tangerang
- yufiastira@gmail.com
- 081310249566

KEMAMPUAN

- •••• Kerja Sama Tim
- •••• Komunikasi
- •••• Mengoperasikan Mesin Bubut CNC
- •••• Mengoperasikan Mesin Bubut milling
- •••• Mengoperasikan Mesin Bubut bor

YUFI ASTIRA

OPERATOR PRODUKSI MACHINING

TENTANG SAYA

Saya adalah pekerja keras, rajin dan disiplin, mampu bekerjasama dengan tim, cepat beradaptasi diri di lingkuang yang baru

DATA PRIBADI

Temppat tanggal lahir: Klaten, 06-09-1993

Jenis kelami : Laki-laki Agama : Islam

Status Perkawinan : Belum kawin

Alamat : Dk. Babad Kardenan Trucuk Klaten
Domisili : Kp Pondok Rt 01 Rw 03 Sindang

jaya, Pasar Kemis Tangerang

PENGALAMAN BEKERJA

Operator Produksi Machining

PT Dian Surya Global | September 2013 - September 2020

- Mengopersikan mesin bubut otomatis CNC
- Mengoperasikan mesin bubut milling
- Mengoperasikan mesin bubut (bor)

RIWAYAT PENDIDIKAN

MAN KARANGANOM KLATEN

ILMU PENGETAHUAN SOSIAL | 2008 - 2011

MTS N 1 TRUCUK

2005 - 2008

MIM BABAD PULUHAN TRUCUK

2000 - 2005



CONTACT ME AT

- Bumi Pasar Kemis Indah,Blok E4 No. 7, Pasar Kemis Tangerang, Indonesia
- vikyyahya.id@gmail.com
- 0895368019831
- www.takcoding.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/vikyyahya-4bb570159/

SKILLS

- •••• Java
- •••• Javascript
- •••• Kotlin
- •••• Php
- •••• Android Development (native)
- • • Mobile Development (react-native)

VIKY YAHYA

MOBILE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm an enthusiastic, responsible and hard working IT person. I am able to work well both in a team environment. I am able to work well under preasure and adhere to strict deadline. I am Mobile Developer since 2019, having good knowledge about Android, strong in algorithm, data structure, object oriented programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Developer (Part Time)

PT. Sinergi Digital Teknologi | Dec 2019 - present

• Development Mobile App (android and ios) at lenna.ai, using android native and react-native.

Fullstack Developer (Internship)

PT. Sinergi Digital Teknologi | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

 Create a web-based auction system use Vue JS and Laravel

Fullstack Developer (Freelance)

Titan Infra Energy | Nov 2019 - Des 2020

 Create web-based refueling management system use Laravel

Administrative Product(Freelance)

PT Diansurya Global | Jul 2018 - Jul 2019

 Create standard operating procedures and make reports on the results of production

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Universitas Muhammadiyah Tangerang

Bachelor Degree Informatics Enginering | Jul 2015 - Nov 2019

• GPA: 3.56

SMK N 1 TRUCUK

BA Product Design | Dec 2008 - Dec 2011